<editor>
    <help>/commander/pages/@PLUGIN_NAME@/@PLUGIN_KEY@_help?s=Administration&amp;ss=Plugins#DeployApplication</help>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Configuration name:</label>
        <property>serverconfig</property>
        <required>1</required>
        <documentation>Name of the configuration to be used. URL and credentials are retrieved from the given configuration. To view or create a new configuration, go to the Administration -> Plugins tab, and select 'Configure' action for @PLUGIN_KEY@ plugin.</documentation>
        <propertyReference>/plugins/@PLUGIN_NAME@/project/jboss_cfgs</propertyReference>
        <htmlDocumentation>Name of the configuration to be used. URL and credentials are retrieved from the given configuration.<br/><br/>A Configuration defines connection details and can be created by going to plugin <a style="text-decoration: none !important; border-bottom-style: dashed; border-bottom-width: thin; font-size: inherit; color: inherit; font-family: inherit; border-color: #d8d8d8; border-spacing: 2px;" target="_blank" href="/commander/pages/@PLUGIN_NAME@/configurations">configuration page</a>.</htmlDocumentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Application Content Source Path:</label>
        <property>applicationContentSourcePath</property>
        <required>1</required>
        <documentation>Usually filepath should be specified here, but it is also possible to provide URL (with special format) from where deployment can be downloaded by JBoss (this URL option will work only for JBoss EAP 7 and later). In case of filepath - pass full filesystem path to the application to deploy. E.g. '/tmp/hello-world.war'. In case of URL (for EAP 7 and later only) - pass URL at which the deployment content is available (NOTE: The expected format in this case should include prefix anchor '--url=', e.g. '--url=https://my.site.com/hello-world.war').</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Deployment Name:</label>
        <property>deploymentName</property>
        <required>0</required>
        <documentation>The unique name of the deployment. If this parameter is not provided then the procedure will retrieve the deployment name based on 'Application Content Source Path' parameter (assuming that some file name specified in 'Application Content Source Path' parameter within file path or url).</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Runtime Name:</label>
        <property>runtimeName</property>
        <required>0</required>
        <documentation>The runtime name for the deployment. NOTE: the file extension (.war, .jar, .ear etc.) needs to be included into runtime name so server can distinguish type of deployment somehow. This would typically be the same as deployment name (see 'Deployment name' parameter), and if not specified the value used for deployment name will be used.</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Enabled Server Groups:</label>
        <property>enabledServerGroups</property>
        <required>0</required>
        <value>--all-server-groups</value>
        <documentation>For Domain only (will be ignored in case of Standalone). The deployment will be assigned (if not assigned yet) to the server groups specified by this parameter and will be enabled on these server groups. Format: comma separated list of server groups (e.g. 'server-group-one,server-group-five') or '--all-server-groups'. If '--all-server-groups' is specified then deployment will be assigned (if not assigned yet) and enabled on all server groups. By default value is set to '--all-server-groups'. If not provided - special assignment with enabling of the deployment will not be performed.</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Disabled Server Groups:</label>
        <property>disabledServerGroups</property>
        <required>0</required>
        <documentation>For Domain only (will be ignored in case of Standalone). The deployment will be assigned (if not assigned yet) to the server groups specified by this parameter and will be disabled on these server groups. Format: comma separated list of server groups (e.g. 'server-group-one,server-group-five') or '--all-server-groups'. If '--all-server-groups' is specified then deployment will be assigned (if not assigned yet) and disabled on all server groups. If not provided - special assignment with disabling of the deployment will not be performed.</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Additional Options:</label>
        <property>additionalOptions</property>
        <required>0</required>
        <documentation>For Standalone only (will be ignored in case of Domain). Currently supported additional option is '--disabled' for Standalone Server: if '--disabled' is specified then the DeployApplication procedure will disable the deployment on standalone server after upgrade (or upload) of the deployment is done, otherwise the procedure will enable the deployment.</documentation>
    </formElement>
</editor>
