<editor>
    <help>https://docs.cloudbees.com/docs/cloudbees-cd/latest/plugins/ec-jboss#StartHostController</help>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Configuration Name:</label>
        <!-- Improvements for CEV-18687 -->
        <configuration>1</configuration>
        <!-- End of improvements for CEV-18687 -->
        <property>serverconfig</property>
        <required>1</required>
        <documentation>Required parameter. Name of the configuration to be used. URL and credentials are retrieved from the given configuration. To view or create a new configuration, go to the Administration -> Plugins tab, and select 'Configure' action for @PLUGIN_KEY@ plugin. NOTE: information for connecting to Master CLI should be provided within the specified configuration, even for stating slave host controllers.</documentation>
        <propertyReference>/plugins/@PLUGIN_NAME@/project/jboss_cfgs</propertyReference>
        <htmlDocumentation>Required parameter. Name of the configuration to be used. URL and credentials are retrieved from the given configuration.<br/><br/>A Configuration defines connection details and can be created by going to plugin <a style="text-decoration: none !important; border-bottom-style: dashed; border-bottom-width: thin; font-size: inherit; color: inherit; font-family: inherit; border-color: #d8d8d8; border-spacing: 2px;" target="_blank" href="/commander/pages/@PLUGIN_NAME@/configurations">configuration page</a>. NOTE: information for connecting to Master CLI should be provided within the specified configuration, even for stating slave host controllers.</htmlDocumentation>
    </formElement>
	<formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Startup Script:</label>
        <property>startupScript</property>
        <required>1</required>
        <documentation>Required parameter. Provide the absolute physical path of the domain script, i.e: 'domain.bat', '/usr/tools/bin/domain.sh', 'c:/Program Files/JBoss/bin/domain.bat'.</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Domain Configuration File:</label>
        <property>domainConfig</property>
        <required>0</required>
        <documentation>Optional Parameter. Applies only to master host controllers. Use this parameter only if you have a need to override the default domain.xml by a different file which stores your domain configuration.</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Host Configuration File:</label>
        <property>hostConfig</property>
        <required>0</required>
        <documentation>Optional Parameter. Use this parameter only if you have a need to override the default host.xml by a different file which stores your host configuration.</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Host Name:</label>
        <property>jbossHostName</property>
        <required>0</required>
        <documentation>Optional parameter. Host Name of the started Host Controller. If provided this parameter would be used to connect using the Master Host Controller Jboss-cli and surface any boot errors upon startup.</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Additional Options:</label>
        <property>additionalOptions</property>
        <required>0</required>
        <documentation>Optional parameter. 'Additional options' to be passed on to domain startup script. If provided parameters will be concatenated AS IS to already generated command line for starting master or slave host controller. These are some examples. 1. '-Djboss.domain.base.dir=/opt/jboss/domain-copied-for-master -b=0.0.0.0 -bmanagement=0.0.0.0'. 2. '-Djboss.domain.base.dir=/opt/jboss/domain-copied-for-slave-1 -Djboss.domain.master.address=some-master-ip -Djboss.management.native.port=12345 -b=0.0.0.0'.</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Log File Location:</label>
        <property>logFileLocation</property>
        <required>0</required>
        <documentation>Optional parameter. Absolute path location to Host controller log file. For example, /opt/jboss/domain-copied-for-slave-1/log/host-controller.log . If provided the procedure will read recent 100 log lines from the specified file surface them as part of the procedure summary logs.</documentation>
    </formElement>
</editor>
