<editor>
    <help>/commander/pages/@PLUGIN_NAME@/@PLUGIN_KEY@_help?s=Administration&amp;ss=Plugins#DeployApplication</help>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Configuration name:</label>
        <!-- Improvements for CEV-18687 -->
        <configuration>1</configuration>
        <!-- End of improvements for CEV-18687 -->
        <property>serverconfig</property>
        <required>1</required>
        <documentation>Name of the configuration to be used. URL and credentials are retrieved from the given configuration. To view or create a new configuration, go to the Administration -> Plugins tab, and select 'Configure' action for @PLUGIN_KEY@ plugin.</documentation>
        <propertyReference>/plugins/@PLUGIN_NAME@/project/jboss_cfgs</propertyReference>
        <htmlDocumentation>Name of the configuration to be used. URL and credentials are retrieved from the given configuration.<br/><br/>A Configuration defines connection details and can be created by going to plugin <a style="text-decoration: none !important; border-bottom-style: dashed; border-bottom-width: thin; font-size: inherit; color: inherit; font-family: inherit; border-color: #d8d8d8; border-spacing: 2px;" target="_blank" href="/commander/pages/@PLUGIN_NAME@/configurations">configuration page</a>.</htmlDocumentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Application Content Source Path:</label>
        <property>applicationContentSourcePath</property>
        <required>1</required>
        <documentation>Either an absolute filepath (including the name of the WAR or EAR) or a URL that the Domain controller or the Standalone Server (as the case may be) can resolve. URL is supported only for 7.0 EAP and later versions. This parameter should be populated as follows. If using filepath, it should be the full filesystem path to the application that needs to be deployed. E.g. '/tmp/hello-world.war'. If using URL it should be preceded by a -- prefix anchor. E.g. '--url=https://my.site.com/hello-world.war'.</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Deployment Name:</label>
        <property>deploymentName</property>
        <required>0</required>
        <documentation>The unique name of the deployment. If this parameter is not passed, it will be derived from 'Application Content Source Path' parameter.</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Runtime Name:</label>
        <property>runtimeName</property>
        <required>0</required>
        <documentation>The runtime name for the deployment. If not specified it will be the same as 'Deployment Name'.</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Enabled Server Groups:</label>
        <property>enabledServerGroups</property>
        <required>0</required>
        <value>--all-server-groups</value>
        <documentation>Applicable to Jboss Domain only. Server groups specified in this parameter will be assigned (if not already assigned) and enabled. These are the formatting rules: Either a comma separated list of server groups (e.g. 'server-group-one,server-group-five') or '--all-server-groups'.</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Disabled Server Groups:</label>
        <property>disabledServerGroups</property>
        <required>0</required>
        <documentation>Applicable to Jboss Domain only. Server groups specified in this parameter will be assigned (if not already assigned) and disabled. These are the formatting rules: Either a comma separated list of server groups (e.g. 'server-group-one,server-group-five') or '--all-server-groups'.</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Additional Options:</label>
        <property>additionalOptions</property>
        <required>0</required>
        <documentation>Applicable to JBoss Standalone only. Currently supported additional option is '--disabled' for Standalone Server. If it is populated as '--disabled' the procedure will deploy the Application and leave it disabled.</documentation>
    </formElement>
</editor>
