<editor>
    <help>/commander/pages/@PLUGIN_NAME@/@PLUGIN_KEY@_help?s=Administration&amp;ss=Plugins#DeployApp</help>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Configuration name:</label>
        <property>serverconfig</property>
        <required>1</required>
        <documentation>Name of the configuration to be used. URL and credentials are retrieved from the given configuration. To view or create a new configuration, go to the Administration -> Plugins tab, and select 'Configure' action for @PLUGIN_KEY@ plugin.</documentation>
        <propertyReference>/plugins/@PLUGIN_NAME@/project/jboss_cfgs</propertyReference>
        <htmlDocumentation>Name of the configuration to be used. URL and credentials are retrieved from the given configuration.<br/><br/>A Configuration defines connection details and can be created by going to plugin <a style="text-decoration: none !important; border-bottom-style: dashed; border-bottom-width: thin; font-size: inherit; color: inherit; font-family: inherit; border-color: #d8d8d8; border-spacing: 2px;" target="_blank" href="/commander/pages/@PLUGIN_NAME@/configurations">configuration page</a>.</htmlDocumentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Physical location of the jboss client script:</label>
        <property>scriptphysicalpath</property>
        <required>0</required>
        <propertyReference type="property">/plugins/@PLUGIN_NAME@/project/jboss_cfgs/$serverconfig/scriptphysicalpath</propertyReference>
        <documentation>Provide the physical location of the jboss Command Line Interface (CLI) script, i.e: 'jboss-cli.bat', '/path/to/jboss-cli.sh'. If omitted, script location from configuration will be used.</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Application Content Source Path:</label>
        <property>warphysicalpath</property>
        <required>1</required>
        <documentation>Either an absolute filepath (including the name of the WAR or EAR) or a URL that the Domain controller or the Standalone Server (as the case may be) can resolve. URL is supported only for 7.0 EAP and later versions. This parameter should be populated as follows. If using filepath, it should be the full filesystem path to the application that needs to be deployed. E.g. '/tmp/hello-world.war'. If using URL it should be preceded by a -- prefix anchor. E.g. '--url=https://my.site.com/hello-world.war'.</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Deployment name:</label>
        <property>appname</property>
        <required>0</required>
        <documentation>Stands for '--name' parameter for jboss-cli 'deploy' command. The unique name of the deployment. If this parameter is not provided then JBoss will retrieve the deployment name from the file name of 'file_path' or '--url'.</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Runtime name for deployment:</label>
        <property>runtimename</property>
        <required>0</required>
        <documentation>The runtime name for the deployment. If not specified it will be the same as 'Deployment Name'.</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <label>Apply to all servers:</label>
        <property>assignallservergroups</property>
        <checkedValue>1</checkedValue>
        <uncheckedValue>0</uncheckedValue>
        <initiallyChecked>1</initiallyChecked>
        <documentation>For Domain only (will be ignored in case of Standalone). Stands for '--all-server-groups' parameter for jboss-cli 'deploy' command. NOTE: this parameter will be ignored if 'Force deployment' is chosen; 'Server groups to apply' will be ignored if this parameter is chosen. This parameter indicates that deploy should apply to all the available server groups.</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Server groups to apply:</label>
        <property>assignservergroups</property>
        <required>0</required>
        <documentation>For Domain only (will be ignored in case of Standalone). Stands for '--server-groups' parameter for jboss-cli 'deploy' command. NOTE: this parameter will be ignored if 'Apply to all servers' or 'Force deployment' is chosen. Provide comma separated list of server group names the deploy command should apply to.</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <label>Force deployment:</label>
        <property>force</property>
        <checkedValue>1</checkedValue>
        <uncheckedValue>0</uncheckedValue>
        <initiallyChecked>0</initiallyChecked>
        <documentation>Stands for '--force' parameter for jboss-cli 'deploy' command. NOTE: in case of JBoss Domain if this parameter is chosen then 'Apply to all servers' and 'Server groups to apply' will be ignored. Chose this option in order to force the replacement of the existing deployment with the one specified in 'file_path' or '--url', see required 'Application Content Source Path' parameter. If 'Force deployment' is Off and the deployment with the specified deployment name (see 'Deployment name' parameter) already exists - deploy will fail and the corresponding message will printed.</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Additional options:</label>
        <property>additional_options</property>
        <required>0</required>
        <documentation>Additional options for jboss-cli 'deploy' command. The 'Additional options' string will be concatenated to already generated command line from the parameters above. NOTE: for JBoss EAP 7 and later do not specify '--url' option here because we have special handling for such option within 'Application Content Source Path' parameter.</documentation>
    </formElement>
</editor>
