<editor>
    <help>/commander/pages/@PLUGIN_NAME@/@PLUGIN_KEY@_help?s=Administration&amp;ss=Plugins#DeployApplication</help>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Configuration name:</label>
        <property>serverconfig</property>
        <required>1</required>
        <documentation>Name of the configuration to be used. URL and credentials are retrieved from the given configuration. To view or create a new configuration, go to the Administration -> Plugins tab, and select 'Configure' action for @PLUGIN_KEY@ plugin.</documentation>
        <propertyReference>/plugins/@PLUGIN_NAME@/project/jboss_cfgs</propertyReference>
        <htmlDocumentation>Name of the configuration to be used. URL and credentials are retrieved from the given configuration.<br/><br/>A Configuration defines connection details and can be created by going to plugin <a style="text-decoration: none !important; border-bottom-style: dashed; border-bottom-width: thin; font-size: inherit; color: inherit; font-family: inherit; border-color: #d8d8d8; border-spacing: 2px;" target="_blank" href="/commander/pages/@PLUGIN_NAME@/configurations">configuration page</a>.</htmlDocumentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Application Content Source Path:</label>
        <property>applicationContentSourcePath</property>
        <required>1</required>
        <documentation>Stands for 'file_path' parameter for jboss-cli 'deploy' command, but it is also possible to provide '--url' parameter here for JBoss EAP 7 and later versions. In case of 'file_path' - pass full filesystem path to the application to deploy, e.g. '/tmp/hello-world.war'. In case of '--url' (for EAP 7 and later) - pass URL at which the deployment content is available (in this case should include prefix anchor '--url=', e.g. '--url=https://my.site.com/hello-world.war').</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Deployment Name:</label>
        <property>deploymentName</property>
        <required>0</required>
        <documentation>Stands for '--name' parameter for jboss-cli 'deploy' command. The unique name of the deployment. If this parameter is not provided then JBoss will retrieve the deployment name from the file name of 'file_path' or '--url'.</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Runtime Name:</label>
        <property>runtimeName</property>
        <required>0</required>
        <documentation>Stands for '--runtime-name' parameter for jboss-cli 'deploy' command. The runtime name for the deployment. NOTE: the file extension (.war, .jar, .ear etc.) needs to be included into runtime name so server can distinguish type of deployment somehow. This would typically be the same as '--name', and if not specified the value used for '--name' will be used.</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Enabled Server Groups:</label>
        <property>enabledServerGroups</property>
        <required>0</required>
        <value>--all-server-groups</value>
        <documentation>For Domain only (will be ignored in case of Standalone). The deployment will be assigned to the server groups specified by this parameter and will be enabled to these server groups. Format: comma separated list of server groups (e.g. 'server-group-one,server-group-five') or '--all-server-groups'. If '--all-server-groups' is specified then deployment will be assigned and enabled on all server groups. By default value is set to '--all-server-groups'. If not provided - special assignment with enabling of the deployment will not be performed.</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Disabled Server Groups:</label>
        <property>disabledServerGroups</property>
        <required>0</required>
        <documentation>For Domain only (will be ignored in case of Standalone). The deployment will be assigned to the server groups specified by this parameter and will be disabled to these server groups. Format: comma separated list of server groups (e.g. 'server-group-one,server-group-five') or '--all-server-groups'. If '--all-server-groups' is specified then deployment will be assigned and disabled on all server groups. If not provided - special assignment with disabling of the deployment will not be performed.</documentation>
    </formElement>
    <formElement>
        <type>entry</type>
        <label>Additional Options:</label>
        <property>additionalOptions</property>
        <required>0</required>
        <documentation>For Standalone only (will be ignored in case of Domain). Currently supported option is '--disabled' for Standalone.</documentation>
    </formElement>
</editor>
